[{"category": "Amazon", "question": "What does AWS stand for?", "options": ["Applications With Servers", "Application Without Servers", "Amazon Web Services", "Amazon Website Systems"], "answer": 2, "difficulty": 200}, {"category": "Amazon", "question": "What is the name of the current CEO and founder of Amazon?", "options": ["Jeff Bezos", "Sundar Pichai", "Reed Hastings", "Mark Zuckerberg"], "answer": 0, "difficulty": 400}, {"category": "Amazon", "question": "Where is the Amazon headquarters located (HQ1)?", "options": ["Silicon Valley", "New York", "Mountain View", "Seattle"], "answer": 3, "difficulty": 600}, {"category": "Amazon", "question": "What items did Amazon start off selling originally?", "options": ["Books", "Radios", "TVs", "Cars"], "answer": 0, "difficulty": 800}, {"category": "Amazon", "question": "What was Amazon's original name?", "options": ["A to Z", "Borders", "Cadabra", "Book World"], "answer": 2, "difficulty": 1000}, {"category": "S3", "question": "What does Amazon S3 stand for?", "options": ["Simple Storage Solution", "Storage Storage Storage (triple redundancy Storage)", "Storage Server Solution", "Simple Storage Service"], "answer": 3, "difficulty": 200}, {"category": "S3", "question": "Object storage systems store files in a flat organization of containers called what?", "options": ["Baskets", "Brackets", "Buckets", "Clusters"], "answer": 2, "difficulty": 400}, {"category": "S3", "question": "Amazon S3 is which type of storage service?", "options": ["Object", "Block", "Simple", "Secure"], "answer": 0, "difficulty": 600}, {"category": "S3", "question": "What is the S3 Durability?", "options": ["99.99%", "99.9999%", "99.999999999%"], "answer": 3, "difficulty": 800}, {"category": "S3", "question": "To protect S3 data from both accidental deletion and accidental overwriting, you should:", "options": ["access S3 data using only signed URLs", "enable S3 versioning on the bucket", "disable S3 delete using an IAM bucket policy", "enable S3 Reduced Redundancy Storage"], "answer": 1, "difficulty": 1000}, {"category": "DynamoDB", "question": "What kind of database is DynamoDB?", "options": ["Relational Database", "Non-relational database", "Search Engine database", "Graph database"], "answer": 1, "difficulty": 200}, {"category": "DynamoDB", "question": "What aspects of a DynamoDB database do NOT need to be defined?", "options": ["Table Name", "Indexes", "Primary Key", "Table Size"], "answer": 3, "difficulty": 400}, {"category": "DynamoDB", "question": "What kind of data store is DynamoDB?", "options": ["Key-Value Store", "Document Store", "Wide Column Store", "File Store"], "answer": 0, "difficulty": 600}, {"category": "DynamoDB", "question": "What kind of data is stored in DynamoDB?", "options": ["Paragraphs", "Buckets", "files", "Items"], "answer": 3, "difficulty": 800}, {"category": "DynamoDB", "question": "Which of the following can NOT be a primary key for a DynamoDB table?", "options": ["a single-attribute String partition key", "a single-attribute Number partition key", "a composite partition-partition key", "a composite partition-sort key"], "answer": 2, "difficulty": 1000}, {"category": "APIGateway", "question": "Can API gateway be used to create unencrypted (HTTP) endpoints?", "options": ["Yes", "No"], "answer": 1, "difficulty": 200}, {"category": "APIGateway", "question": "Which of the below is an API type supported by API Gateway?", "options": ["SOAP", "XML-RPC", "JSON-RPC", "REST"], "answer": 3, "difficulty": 400}, {"category": "APIGateway", "question": "Which of the below is a benefit of using API Gateway?", "options": ["Caching API responses", "IP blacklisting", "Intrusion prevention", "Load balancing"], "answer": 0, "difficulty": 600}, {"category": "APIGateway", "question": "What is an API Gateway Stage?", "options": ["The method response types, their headers and content types", "The format/schema/shape of some data", "The path through which an API deployment is accessible", "The combination of a resource path and an HTTP verb, such as GET, POST, and DELETE"], "answer": 2, "difficulty": 800}, {"category": "APIGateway", "question": "What year was Amazon API Gateway launched?", "options": ["2006", "2012", "2015", "2017"], "answer": 2, "difficulty": 1000}, {"category": "Lambda", "question": "Which of the languages below AWS Lambda does not support natively?", "options": ["Go", "PowerShell", "Ruby", "Perl"], "answer": 3, "difficulty": 200}, {"category": "Lambda", "question": "What is the maximum amount of time that a lambda function can take to execute?", "options": ["3 minutes", "5 minutes", "15 minutes", "30 minutes"], "answer": 2, "difficulty": 400}, {"category": "Lambda", "question": "How can I share state data between lambda function executions?", "options": ["Save the information to the disk", "Save the information to the /tmp directory", "Leverage other web services, such as Amazon S3 or Dynamo DB"], "answer": 2, "difficulty": 600}, {"category": "Lambda", "question": "How can you scale a lambda function?", "options": ["AWS does it automatically", "Setup auto-scaling for the lambda function", "Create an auto-scaling group, and assign the lambda function to it"], "answer":0, "difficulty": 800}, {"category": "Lambda", "question": "How can you access the infrastructure that AWS Lambda runs on?", "options": ["Provision and assign an EC2 instance for the lambda to run on and then you can access it", "Check the AWS Lambda console for the EC2 instance it runs on, and do ssh", "Via the AWS Lambda console", "It is not possible to access the infrastructure"], "answer": 3, "difficulty": 1000}]